Department of Languages, Literature and Linguistics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Department of Languages, Literature and Linguistics fonds
1964 - 1988
F-13
2.25 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Department of Languages, Literature and Linguistics
The Department of Languages, Literatures and Linguistics was established by the Board of Governors in 1965 under the name of the Department of Modern Languages. The Department was responsible, through its Head, for the promotion of research and the development and delivery of programs in the discipline of languages and linguistics. Initially, the Department offered a B.A. program in four language divisions— French, German, Russian, and Spanish— or in linguistics. In 1966, a M.A. in Linguistics was introduced, followed in 1967 by a Ph.D. program. The curricula developed and expanded steadily and by 1970, language courses consisted of three sections: the language itself, linguistics, and literature. While the French and Spanish programs expanded, the German and Russian divisions had smaller enrollments and faculty allocations were reduced. In 1974, an M.A. (Teaching French) program was added and in 1980 the French Language Training Centre was opened. In 1978, the Department was renamed Languages, Literatures and Linguistics, and in 1989 it was disbanded. Upon its dissolution, the Department was replaced by the Departments of French, Linguistics, and Spanish and Latin American Studies. All other language instruction, including Chinese, Hindi, Italian, Latin, and Swahili, was moved to the Division of Interdisciplinary Studies in the Faculty of Arts.
The Department was initially organized administratively into a Chair, four sub-departments or divisions (French, German, Russian, and Spanish), and a number of standing committees. The Chair was the chief administrative officer, whose responsibilities included the management of the operational budget; faculty tenure, promotion and salary recommendations; teaching assignments; and representation of the Department to external bodies. While the Chair had overall responsibility to the Department and the Dean of Arts for the efficient operation of the Department, most decisions were made at the committee level with major issues referred to departmental meetings. The Departmental Assistant was responsible for much of the day-to-day administration of the Department, which included the management of the departmental budget, the scheduling of courses, the provision of liaison with administrative offices, and advising students.
The number and composition of departmental committees varied over time. In 1966, there were eleven committees, including the Departmental Advisory, Scholarship, Library, Graduate Studies, Curriculum, Journal, Promotions, Projects, Amerindian, Teaching Experiments and Textbook, and Laboratory committees. There were also departmental meetings under the name of the Plenary committee. By 1969, the number of committees had been reduced to four, including the Committee of Chairmen, Graduate Studies, Tenure, and Salaries. The number of divisions within the Department had also expanded to five to include Linguistics, and each of these bodies conducted its own meetings under the leadership of a director who reported to the departmental chair. At the time of an external review in 1975, the significant change to the committees structure was the addition of a Committee of Chairmen -- consisting of the Department Chair, the Departmental Assistant, the five divisional directors, and the chair of the Graduate Studies committee -- and Tenure, Promotion, and Salaries committees. Throughout its history, the Department formed ad hoc committees when required.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of its creator.
The fonds of the Department of Languages, Literatures and Linguistics consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the department and the carrying out of its functions of providing instruction and promoting research. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, initiation and administration of curriculum and programs; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; departmental reviews; and the publication of journals and reports. The types of documents include meeting agenda, annual reports, correspondence, course outlines and examinations, faculty files, memoranda, minutes of meetings, and reports.
The titles and arrangement of series were provided by the archivist.
Bouton, Charles P.; Harden, Evelyn; Lincoln, Neville J.; Bird, Genevieve C.; Bursill-Hall, Geoffrey L.
The records were transferred in a number of accessions from the Department beginning in the early 1980s.
All accessions have been processed as of May 2004. No further accruals are expected.
Consult the records of the Departments of French, Humanities, and Linguistics, as well as the Programs in Latin American Studies and Spanish. Also consult the inventory of the Faculty of Arts fonds, F-2.
Some access restrictions apply in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the appropriate series level description and the archivist.
File lists are available.
- Programs and committees, 1965 - 1986; F-13-1; 57 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to committees and the different programs offered by the Department. It includes meeting agenda and minutes, correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  - French division, 1969 - 1980; F-13-1-1; 4 cm of textual records
    - French division meetings, 1969 - 1972; F-13-1-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
      Textual records
      Pending review
    - French division meetings, 1973 - 1974; F-13-1-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
    - French division meetings, 1975 - 1977; F-13-1-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
    - French division meetings, 1978 - 1980; F-13-1-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
  - German division, 1969 - 1986; F-13-1-2; 4 cm of textual records
    - German division meetings, 1969 - 1976; F-13-1-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
    - German division meetings, 1980; F-13-1-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
    - German search committee, 1976 - 1977; F-13-1-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
    - Publications -Simplicissimus, 1983 - 1986; F-13-1-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
      Open
  - Russian division, 1969 - 1978; F-13-1-3; 1 cm of textual records
    - Russian division meetings, 1969 - 1978; F-13-1-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
  - Spanish division, 1969 - 1979; F-13-1-4; 3 cm of textual records
    - Spanish division meetings, 1969 - 1971; F-13-1-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
    - Spanish division meetings, 1972 - 1977; F-13-1-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
    - Spanish division meetings, 1978 - 1979; F-13-1-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
  - Linguistics division, 1969 - 1980; F-13-1-5; 3 cm of textual records
    - Linguistics division meetings, 1969 - 1972; F-13-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
    - Linguistics division meetings, 1973 - 1977; F-13-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
    - Linguistics division meetings, 1978 - 1980; F-13-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
  - Graduate studies committee, 1967 - 1980; F-13-1-6; 11 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1967 - 1974; F-13-1-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
    - Correspondence, 1975 - 1976; F-13-1-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
    - Correspondence, 1977; F-13-1-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
    - Correspondence, 1978 - 1980; F-13-1-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1969 - 1971; F-13-1-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1972 - 1973; F-13-1-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1974 - 1975; F-13-1-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-2)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1976 - 1977; F-13-1-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-3)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1978 - 1979; F-13-1-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 13-3)
  - Plenary, 1965 - 1979; F-13-1-7; 19 cm of textual records
    - General meetings, 1965 - 1967; F-13-1-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-3)
    - General meetings, 1968; F-13-1-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-3)
    - General meetings, 1968; F-13-1-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-3)
    - Plenary meetings, 1969; F-13-1-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-3)
    - Plenary meetings, 1970; F-13-1-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-3)
    - Plenary meetings, 1971; F-13-1-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-3)
    - Plenary meetings, 1972; F-13-1-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-3)
    - Plenary meetings, 1973; F-13-1-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
    - Plenary meetings, 1974; F-13-1-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
    - Plenary meetings, 1975; F-13-1-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
    - Plenary meetings, 1976; F-13-1-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
    - Plenary meetings, 1977; F-13-1-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
    - Plenary meetings, 1978; F-13-1-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
    - Plenary meetings, 1979; F-13-1-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
  - Committee of chairmen, 1969 - 1981; F-13-1-8; 5 cm of textual records
    - Committee of chairmen, 1969 - 1971; F-13-1-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
    - Committee of chairmen, 1972 - 1974; F-13-1-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
    - Committee of chairmen, 1975 - 1977; F-13-1-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-4)
    - Committee of chairmen, 1978 - 1981; F-13-1-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
  - Committee on goals and objectives, 1974; F-13-1-9; 1 cm of textual records
    - Committee on goals and objectives, 1974; F-13-1-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
  - Chinese, 1978; F-13-1-10; 1 cm of textual records
    - Chinese, 1978; F-13-1-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
  - French Language Training Centre, 1978 - 1980; F-13-1-11; 1 cm of textual records
    - French Language Training Centre, 1978 - 1980; F-13-1-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
  - Committees, 1965 - 1980; F-13-1-12; 5 cm of textual records
    - Advisory committee, 1965 - 1968; F-13-1-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Senior committee, 1967; F-13-1-12-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Curriculum committee on undergraduate studies, 1977; F-13-1-12-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Amerindian committee, 1968; F-13-1-12-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Literature committee, 1967 - 1968; F-13-1-12-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Committee on language teaching and applied linguistics, 1980; F-13-1-12-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Committee on transfer credits and course challenge policy, 1974; F-13-1-12-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
  - Departmental committees, 1965 - 1976; F-13-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-1)
- Administration, 1964 - 1982; F-13-2; 44 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the administration of the Department, including budgeting, staffing, and policy formulation. It includes annual reports, constitutions, correspondence, course outlines and schedules, memoranda, policies and procedures, press releases, and reports.
  Access to records in the subseries "Support, administrative and professional staff" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Subject files, 1964 - 1981; F-13-2-1; 20 cm of textual records
    - Accommodation, 1965 - 1977; F-13-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Accommodation, 1978 - 1981; F-13-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Annual reports, 1966 - 1971; F-13-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Calendar changes, 1968 - 1977; F-13-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Course descriptions, 1969; F-13-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Courses and schedules, 1968 - 1973; F-13-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
    - Courses and schedules, 1974 - 1977; F-13-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Courses and schedules, 1978 - 1980; F-13-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Course offerings, 1976 - 1977; F-13-2-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Curriculum goals, 1967; F-13-2-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Department name change, 1973 - 1977; F-13-2-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Departmental organization, 1968; F-13-2-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - English Department, 1974 - 1977; F-13-2-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Enrolment statistics, 1965 - 1976; F-13-2-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Language labs, 1965 - 1972; F-13-2-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Languages lab renovation, 1973 - 1974; F-13-2-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Languages lab reorganization, 1974 - 1977; F-13-2-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973 - 1977; F-13-2-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Non-credit courses, 1973 - 1974; F-13-2-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Office of international education proposal, 1970; F-13-2-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Open House, 1975; F-13-2-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Pensions, 1967; F-13-2-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Press releases, 1964 - 1966; F-13-2-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Registration, 1970 - 1981; F-13-2-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 13-6)
    - Senate - Russian and German programs, 1976 - 1979; F-13-2-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - Space requirements, 1966 - 1967; F-13-2-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - Transfer credit, advanced credit, 1968 - 1980; F-13-2-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - University review committee, 1977 - 1978; F-13-2-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
  - Policies and procedures, 1966 - 1978; F-13-2-2; 2 cm of textual records
    - Policies and procedures, 1966 - 1967; F-13-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - Policies, procedures, constitutions, 1974 - 1978; F-13-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - Ad hoc committee on policy and procedures, 1967; F-13-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
  - Budget, 1967 - 1980; F-13-2-3; 1 cm of textual records
    - Budget, 1967 - 1977; F-13-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - Budget, 1978 - 1980; F-13-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
  - Chairmanship, 1973 - 1982; F-13-2-4; 1 cm of textual records
    - Chairmanship, 1973 - 1978; F-13-2-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - Chairman's correspondence, 1978 - 1982; F-13-2-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
  - Support, administrative and professional staff, 1966 - 1982; F-13-2-5; 1 cm of textual records
    - Support, Administrative and Professional Staff (APSA), 1973 - 1982; F-13-2-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - Staff salaries, 1966 - 1967; F-13-2-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
  - Teaching and language assistants, 1967 - 1976; F-13-2-6; 2 cm of textual records
    - Teaching assistants, 1967; F-13-2-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - Teaching/language assistants, 1975 - 1976; F-13-2-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - T.A. traineeships, 1974; F-13-2-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
  - Conferences and invited speakers, 1966 - 1981; F-13-2-7; 7 cm of textual records
    - Conferences, 1976 - 1978; F-13-2-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-7)
    - Visiting speakers, 1966 - 1974; F-13-2-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-8)
    - Visiting speakers, 1975 - 1977; F-13-2-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-8)
    - Visiting speakers, 1978 - 1980; F-13-2-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-8)
    - Program of distinction, 1979 - 1981; F-13-2-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-8)
  - Departmental reviews, 1975; F-13-2-8; 8 cm of textual records
    - External review - papers I, 1975; F-13-2-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-8)
    - External review - papers II, 1975; F-13-2-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-8)
    - External review - papers III, 1975; F-13-2-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-8)
    - External review - papers IV, 1975; F-13-2-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-8)
    - External review - papers V, 1975; F-13-2-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - External review - reports, 1975; F-13-2-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
  - Administration, 1975 - 1981; F-13-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-5)
- Faculty members, 1964 - 1983; F-13-3; 81 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the appointment of faculty members. It includes case files, correspondence, curricula vitae, memoranda, and reports.
  Case files are arranged alphabetically by name of faculty member.
  Access to records in this series is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Faculty members, 1964 - 1983; F-13-3-1; 49 cm of textual records
    - Faculty - A, 1979; F-13-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - A, 1965 - 1970; F-13-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - A, 1971 - 1973; F-13-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - A, 1974 - 1975; F-13-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - A, 1976 - 1977; F-13-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - B, 1966 - 1974; F-13-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - B, 1974 - 1977; F-13-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - B, 1964 - 1971; F-13-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - B, 1975 - 1977; F-13-3-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - C, 1966 - 1967; F-13-3-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - C, 1973 - 1974; F-13-3-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - C, 1965 - 1982; F-13-3-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - C, 1965 - 1968; F-13-3-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
    - Faculty - D, 1965 - 1969; F-13-3-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - L, 1967 - 1970; F-13-3-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - D, 1966; F-13-3-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - D, 1966 - 1968; F-13-3-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - E, 1966 - 1968; F-13-3-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - F, 1966 - 1970; F-13-3-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - G, 1979 - 1980; F-13-3-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - G, 1966 - 1976; F-13-3-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - G, 1970 - 1978; F-13-3-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - G, 1966 - 1974; F-13-3-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 13-10)
    - Faculty - H, 1970; F-13-3-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - H, 1966 - 1970; F-13-3-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - H, 1965 - 1972; F-13-3-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - H, 1977 - 1980; F-13-3-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - J, 1970; F-13-3-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - K, 1975; F-13-3-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - K, 1973 - 1976; F-13-3-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - K, 1978 - 1980; F-13-3-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - K, 1976 - 1979; F-13-3-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - K, 1976 - 1977; F-13-3-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - M, 1966 - 1967; F-13-3-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - M, 1976; F-13-3-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - M, 1977; F-13-3-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - M, 1974; F-13-3-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - M, 1967 - 1977; F-13-3-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - M, 1976 - 1977; F-13-3-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - N, 1978; F-13-3-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - N, 1965 - 1983; F-13-3-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 13-11)
    - Faculty - O, 1971; F-13-3-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - O, 1966 - 1968; F-13-3-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - P, 1966 - 1967; F-13-3-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - R, 1978; F-13-3-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - R, 1977 - 1978; F-13-3-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - S, 1970 - 1971; F-13-3-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - S, 1965 - 1981; F-13-3-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - S, 1967 - 1970; F-13-3-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - S, 1974 - 1976; F-13-3-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - T, 1975; F-13-3-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - T, 1969 - 1970; F-13-3-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - V, 1973 - 1980; F-13-3-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - V, 1972 - 1981; F-13-3-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - V, 1975 - 1979; F-13-3-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - V, 1970 - 1976; F-13-3-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - W, 1977; F-13-3-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - W, 1978 - 1980; F-13-3-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - W, 1965 - 1975; F-13-3-1-0-59 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
    - Faculty - W, 1970 - 1974; F-13-3-1-0-60 (Archival box - standard 13-12)
  - Faculty workload, 1971 - 1979; F-13-3-2; 2 cm of textual records
    - Faculty workload, 1971 - 1979; F-13-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Teaching contact hours, 1974; F-13-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
  - Faculty responsibilities, 1970 - 1979; F-13-3-3; 2 cm of textual records
    - Faculty responsibilities, 1977 - 1979; F-13-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Faculty duty/research, 1970; F-13-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
  - Appointments and hiring, 1966 - 1980; F-13-3-4; 9 cm of textual records
    - Appointment, hiring procedures, 1973 - 1980; F-13-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Appointments, 1966; F-13-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Faculty appointments, 1973; F-13-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Faculty appointments, 1974; F-13-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Faculty appointments, 1975; F-13-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Faculty appointments, 1976; F-13-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Faculty appointments, 1977; F-13-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Faculty appointments, 1978; F-13-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Recruitment, 1978 - 1980; F-13-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Faculty positions, 1977 - 1978; F-13-3-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
    - Faculty positions, 1979 - 1980; F-13-3-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 13-13)
  - Salaries and honoraria, 1965 - 1981; F-13-3-5; 7 cm of textual records
    - Faculty salaries, 1966 - 1967; F-13-3-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Salaries - academic and administrative, 1966 - 1972; F-13-3-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Salaries committee, 1965 - 1969; F-13-3-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Salaries committee, 1970 - 1972; F-13-3-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Salaries committee, 1973 - 1974; F-13-3-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Salaries committee, 1975; F-13-3-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-14)